<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>sky-line</title>
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-27T14:25:42.404Z</updated>
  <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>NetWilliam</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Born to Win</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/27/Born-to-Win/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/27/Born-to-Win/</id>
    <published>2017-03-27T14:10:37.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-27T14:25:42.404Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Born-to-Win"><a href="#Born-to-Win" class="headerlink" title="Born to Win"></a>Born to Win</h2><p>Each human being is born as something new, something that never existed before. Each is born with the capacity to win at life. Each person has a unique way of seeing, hearing, touching, tasting and thinking. Each has his or her own unique potentials - capabilities and limitations. Each can be a significant, thinking, aware, and creative being - a productive person, a winner.</p>
<p>The word “winner” and “loser” have many meanings. When we refer to a person as a winner, we do not mean one who makes someone else lose. To us, a winner is one who responds authentically by being credible, trustworthy, responsive, and genuine, both as an individual and as a member of a society.</p>
<p>Winners do not dedicate their lives to a concept of what whey imagine they should be; rather, they are themselves and as such do not use their energy putting on a performance, maintaining pretence and mainipulating others. They are aweare that there is a difference between being loving and acting loving, between being stupid and acting stupid, between being knowledgeable and acting knowledgeable. Winner do not need to hide behind a mask.</p>
<p>Winners are not afraid to do their own thinking and to use their own knowledge. They can separate facts from opinions and don’t pretend to have all the answers. They listen to others, evaluate what they say, but come to their own conclusions. Although winners can admire and respect other people, they are not totally defined, demolished, bound or awed by them.</p>
<p>Winners do not play “helpless”, nor do they play the blaming game. Instead, they assume responsibility for their own lives. They don’t give others a false authority over them. Winners are their own bosses and know it.</p>
<p>A winner’s timing is right. Winners respond appropriately to the situation. Their responses are related to the message sent and preserve the significance, worth, well-being, and dignity of the people involved. Winners know that for everything there is a season and for every activity a time.</p>
<p>Although Winners can freely enjoy themselves, they can also postpone enjoyment, can discipline themselves in the present to enhance their enjoyment in the future. Winners are not afraid to go after what he wants, but they do so in proper ways. Winners do not get their security by controlling others. They do not set themselves up to lose.</p>
<p>A winner cares about the world and its peoples. A winner is not isolated from the general problems of society, but is concerned, compassionate, and committed to improving the quality of life. Even in the face of national and international adversity, a winner’s self-image is not one of a powerless individual. A winner works to make the world a better place.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Born-to-Win&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Born-to-Win&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Born to Win&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Born to Win&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each human being is born as someth
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Facing the Enemies Within</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/26/Facing-the-Enemies-Within/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/26/Facing-the-Enemies-Within/</id>
    <published>2017-03-26T09:17:21.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-26T09:32:22.901Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Facing-the-Enemies-Within"><a href="#Facing-the-Enemies-Within" class="headerlink" title="Facing the Enemies Within"></a>Facing the Enemies Within</h2><p>We are not born with courage, but neither are we born with fear. Maybe some of our fears are brought on by your own experiences, by what someone has told you, by what you’ve read in the papers. Some fears are valid, like walking alone in a bad part of town at two o’clock in the morning. But once you learn to avoid that situation, you won’t need to live in fear of it.</p>
<p>Fears, even the most basic ones, can totally destory our ambitions. Fear can destory fortunes. Fear can destory relationships. Fear, if left unchecked, can destory our lives. Fears is one of the many enemies lurking inside us.</p>
<p>Let me tell you about five of the other enemies we face from within. The first enemy that you’ve got to destory before it destorys you is indifference. What a tragic disease this is! “Ho-hum, let it slide. I’ll just dritf along.” Here’s one problem with drifting: you can’t dritf your way to the top of the mountain.</p>
<p>The second enemy we face is indecision. Indecision is the thief of opportunity and enterprise. It will steal your chances for a better future. Take a sword to this enemy.</p>
<p>The third enemy inside is doubt. Sure, there’s room for healthy skepticism. You can’t believe everything. But you also can’t let doubt take over. Many people doubt the past, doubt the future, doubt each other, doubt the government, doubt the possibilities and doubt the opportunities. Worse of all, they doubt themselves. I’m telling you, doubt will destory your life and your changces of success. It will empty both your bank account and your heart. Doubt is an enemy. Go after it. Get rid of it.</p>
<p>The fourth enemy within is worry. We’ve all got to worry some. Just don’t let it conquer you. Instead, let it alarm you. Worry can be useful. If you step off the curb in New York City and a taxi is coming. you’ve got to worry. But you can’t let worry loose like a mad dog that drives you into a small corner. Here’s what you’ve got to do with your worries: drive them into a small corner. Whatever is out to get you, you’ve got to get it. Whatever is pushing on you, you’ve got to push back.</p>
<p>The fifth interior enemy is overcaution. It is the timid approach to life. Timidity is not a virtue; it’s an illness. If you let it go, it’ll conquer you. Timid people don’t get promoted. They don’t advance and grow and become powerful in the marketplace. You’ve got to avoid overcaution.</p>
<p>Do battle with the enemy. Do battle with your fears. Build your courage to fight what’s holding you back, what’s keeping you from your goals and dreams. Be courageous in your life and in your pursuit of the things you want and the person you want to become.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Facing-the-Enemies-Within&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Facing-the-Enemies-Within&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Facing the Enemies Within&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Facing the 
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>First Inaugural Address</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/14/First-Inaugural-Address/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/14/First-Inaugural-Address/</id>
    <published>2017-03-13T17:27:05.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-13T17:43:28.211Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="First-Inaugural-Address-Excerpts"><a href="#First-Inaugural-Address-Excerpts" class="headerlink" title="First Inaugural Address (Excerpts)"></a>First Inaugural Address (Excerpts)</h2><p>We observe today not a victory of party, but a celebration of freedom, symbolizing an end, as well as a beginning; signifying renewal, as well as change. For I have sworn before you and Almighty God the same solemn oath our forebears prescribed nearly a century and three quarters ago.</p>
<p>……</p>
<p>In your hands, my fellow citizens, more than in mine, will rest the final success or failure of our course. Since this country was founded, each generation of Americans has been summoned to give testimony to its national loyalty. The graves of young Americans who answered the call to service surround the globe.</p>
<p>Now the trumpet summons us again, not as a call to bear arms, though arms we need; not as a call to battle, though embattled we are; but a call to bear the burden of a long twilight struggle, year in and year out, “rejoicing in hope; patient in tribulation”, a struggle against the common enemies of man: tyranny, poverty, disease, and war itself.</p>
<p>Can we forge against these enemies a grand and global alliance, North and south, East and West, that can assure a more fruitful life for all mankind? Will you join in that historic effort?</p>
<p>In the long history of the world, only a few generations have been granted the role of defending freedom in its  hour of maximum danger. I do not shrink from this responsibility. I welcome it. I do not believe that any of us would exchange places with any other people or any other generation. The energy, the faith, the devotion which we bring to this endeavor will light our country and all who serve it. And the glow from that fire can truly light the world.</p>
<p>And so, my fellow Americans, ask not what your country can do for you, ask what you can do for your country.</p>
<p>My fellow citizens of the world, ask not what America will do for you, but what together we can do for the freedom of man.</p>
<p>Finally, whether you are citizens of America or citizens of the world, ask of us here the same high standards of strength and sacrifice which we ask of you. With a good conscience our only sure reward, with history the final judge of our deeds, let us go forth to lead the land we love, asking His blessing and His help, but knowing that here on earth, God’s work must truly be our own.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;First-Inaugural-Address-Excerpts&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#First-Inaugural-Address-Excerpts&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;First Inaugural Address (Exc
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Ambition</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/12/Ambition/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/12/Ambition/</id>
    <published>2017-03-12T04:08:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-12T04:40:24.598Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Ambition"><a href="#Ambition" class="headerlink" title="Ambition"></a>Ambition</h2><p>It is not difficult to imagine a world short of ambition. It would probably be a kinder world: without demands, without abrasions, without disappointments. People would have time for reflection. Such work as they did would not be for themselves but for the collectivity. Competition would never enter in. Conflict would be eliminated, tension become a thing of the past. The stress of creation would be at an end. Art would no longer be troubling, but purely celebratory in its functions. Longevity would be increased, for fewer people would die of heart attack or stroke caused by tumultuous endeavor. Anxiety would be extinct. Time would stretch on and on, with ambition long departed from the human heart.</p>
<p>Ah, how unrelievedly boring life would be!</p>
<p>There is a strong view that holds that success is a myth, and ambition therefore a sham. Does this mean that success does not really exist? That achievement is at bottom empty? That the efforts of men and women are of no significance alongside the force of movements and events? Now not all success, obviously, is worth esteeming, nor all ambition worth cultivating. Which are and which are not is something one soon enough learns on one’s own. But event the most cynical secretly admit that success exists; that achievement counts for a great deal; and that the true myth is that the actions of men and women are useless. To believe otherwise is to take on a point of view that is likely to be deranging. It is, in its implications. to remove all motives for competence, interest in attainment, and regard for posterity.</p>
<p>We do not choose to be born. We do not choose our parents. We do not choose our historical epoch, the country of our birth, or the immediate circumstances of our upbringing. We do not, most of us, choose to die; nor do we choose the time or conditions of our death. But within all this realm of choicelessness, we do choose how we shall live: courageously or in cowardice, honorably or dishonorably, with purpose or in drift. We decide what is important and what is trivial in life. We decide that what makes us significant is either what we do or what we refuse to do. But no matter how indifferent the universe may be to our choices and decisions, these choices and decisions are ours to make. We decide. We choose. And as we decide and choose, so are our lives formed. In the end, forming our own destiny is what ambition is about.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Ambition&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Ambition&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Ambition&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Ambition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is not difficult to imagine a world short o
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>If I Rest, I Rust</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/11/If-I-Rest-I-Rust/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/11/If-I-Rest-I-Rust/</id>
    <published>2017-03-11T06:13:36.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-21T01:20:31.761Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="If-I-Rest-I-Rust"><a href="#If-I-Rest-I-Rust" class="headerlink" title="If I Rest, I Rust"></a>If I Rest, I Rust</h2><p>The significant inscription found on an old key - “If I rest, I rust” - would be an excellent motto for those who are afflicted with the slightest bit of idleness. Even the most industrious person might adopt it with advantage to serve as a reminder that, if one allows his faculties to rest, like the iron in the unused key, they will soon show signs of rust and, ultimately, cannot do the work required of them.</p>
<p>Those who would attain the heights reached and kept by great men must keep their faculties polished by constant use, so that they may unlock the doors of knowledge, the gates that guard the entrances to the professions, to science, art, literature, agriculture - every department of human endeavor.</p>
<p>Industry keeps bright the key that opens the treasury of achievement. If Hugh Miller, after toiling all day in a quarry, had devoted his evenings to rest and recreation, he would never have become a famous geologist. The celebrated mathematician, Edmund Stone, would never have published a mathematical dictionary, never have found the key to science of mathematics, if he had given his spare moments to idleness. Had the little Scotch lad, Ferguson, allowed the busy brain to go to sleep while he tended sheep on the hillside, instead of calculating the position of the stars by a string of beads, he would never have become a famous astronomer.</p>
<p>Labor vanquishes all - not inconstant, spasmodic, or ill-directed labor; but faithful, unremitting, daily effort toward a well-directed purpose. Just as truly as eternal vigilance is the price of liberty, so is eternal industry the price of noble and enduring success.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;If-I-Rest-I-Rust&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#If-I-Rest-I-Rust&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;If I Rest, I Rust&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;If I Rest, I Rust&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signific
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Companionship of Books</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/08/Companionship-of-Books/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/08/Companionship-of-Books/</id>
    <published>2017-03-07T17:27:48.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-21T01:13:21.898Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Companionship-of-Books-Excerpts"><a href="#Companionship-of-Books-Excerpts" class="headerlink" title="Companionship of Books (Excerpts)"></a>Companionship of Books (Excerpts)</h2><p>A man may usually be known by the books he reads as well as by the company he keeps; for there is a companionship of books as well as of men; and one should always live in the best company, whether it be of books or of men.</p>
<p>A good book may be among the best of friends. It is the same today that it always was, and it will never change. It is the most patient and cheerful of companions. It does not turn its back upon us  in times of adversity or distress. It always receives us with the same kindness; amusing and instructing us in youth, and comforting and consoling us in age.</p>
<p>Men often discover their affinity to each other by the mutual love they have for a book just as two persons sometimes discover a friend by the admiration which both entertain for a third. There is an old proverb, “Love me, love my dog.” But there is more wisdom in this: “Love me, love my book.” The book is a truer and higher bond of union. Men can think, feel, and sympathize with each other through their favorite author. They live in him together, and he in them.</p>
<p>A good book is often the best urn of a life enshrining the best that life could think out; for the world of a man’s life is, for the most part, but the world of his thoughts. Thus the best books are treasuries of good words, the golden thoughts, which, remembered and cherished, become our constant companions and comforters.</p>
<p>Books possess an essence of immortality. They are by far the most lasting products of human effort. Temples and statues decay, but books survive. Time is of no account with great thoughts, which are as fresh today as when they first passed through their author’s minds, ages ago. What was then said and thought still speaks to us as vividly as ever from the printed page. The only effect of time has been to sift out the bad products; for nothing in literature can long survive but what is really good.</p>
<p>Books introduce us into the best society; they bring us into the presence of the greatest minds that have ever lived. We hear what they said and did; we see them as if they were really alive; we sympathize with them, enjoy with them, grieve with them; their experience becomes ours, and we feel as if we were in a measure actors with them in the scenes which they describe.</p>
<p>The great and good do not die, even in this world. Embalmed in books, their spirits walk abroad. The book is a living voice. It is an intellect to which one still listens.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Companionship-of-Books-Excerpts&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Companionship-of-Books-Excerpts&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Companionship of Books (Excerp
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Three Days to See</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/08/Three-Days-to-See/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/08/Three-Days-to-See/</id>
    <published>2017-03-07T16:40:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-11T05:55:04.863Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Three-Days-to-See-Excerpts"><a href="#Three-Days-to-See-Excerpts" class="headerlink" title="Three Days to See (Excerpts)"></a>Three Days to See (Excerpts)</h2><p>All of us have read thrilling stories in which the hero had only a limited and specified time to live. Sometimes it was as long as a year; sometimes as short as twenty-four hours. But always we were interested in discovering just how the doomed man chose to spend his last days or his last hours. I speak, of course, of free men who have a choice, not condemned criminals whose sphere of activities is strictly delimited.</p>
<p>Such stories set us thinking, wondering what we should do under similar circumstances. What events, what experiences, what associations should we crowd into those last hours as mortal beings? What happiness should we find in reviewing the past, what regrets?</p>
<p>Sometimes I have thought it would be an excellent rule to live each day as if we should die tomorrow. Such an attitude would emphasize sharply the values of life. We should live each day with gentleness, vigor, and a keenness of appreciation which are often lost when time streches before us in the constant panorama of more days and months and years to come. There are those, of course, who would adopt the Epicurean motto of “Eat, drink, and be merry.” But most people would be chastened by the certainty of impending death.</p>
<p>In stories the doomed hero is usually saved at the last minute by some stroke of fortune, but almost always his sense of values is changed. He becomes more appreciative of the meaning of life and its permanent spiritual values. It has often been noted that those who live, or have lived, in the shadow of death bring a mellow sweetness to everything they do.</p>
<p>Most of us, however, take life for granted. We know that one day we must die, but usually we picture that day as far in future. When we are in buoyant health, death is all but unimaginable. We seldom think of it. The days stretch out in an endless vista. So we go about our petty tasks, hardly aware of our listless attitude toward life.</p>
<p>The same lethargy, I am afraid, characterizes the use of all our faculties and senses. Only the deaf appreciate hearing, only the blind realize the manifold blessings that lie in sight. Particularly does this observation apply to those who have lost sight and hearing in adult life. But those who have never suffered impairment of sight or hearing seldom make the fullest use of these blessed faculties. Their eyes and ears take in all sights and sounds hazily, without concentration and with little appreciation. It is the same old story of not being grateful for what we have until we lose it, of not being conscious of health until we are ill.</p>
<p>I have often thought it would be a blessing if each human being were stricken blind and deaf for a few days at some time during his early adult life. Darkness would make him more appreciative of sight; silence would teach him the joys of sound.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Three-Days-to-See-Excerpts&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Three-Days-to-See-Excerpts&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Three Days to See (Excerpts)&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Three 
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Gettysburg Address</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/01/Gettysburg-Address/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/03/01/Gettysburg-Address/</id>
    <published>2017-02-28T16:11:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-17T19:00:02.247Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Gettysburg-Address"><a href="#Gettysburg-Address" class="headerlink" title="Gettysburg Address"></a>Gettysburg Address</h2><p>Four score and seven years ago our fathers brought forth on this continent, a new nation, conceived in Liberty, and dedicated to the proposition that all men are created equal.</p>
<p>Now we are engaged in a great civil war, testing whether that nation, or any nation so conceived and so dedicated, can long endure. We are met on a great battle-field of that war. We have come to dedicate a portion of that field, as a final resting place for those who here gave their lives that that nation might live. It is altogether fitting and proper that we should do this.</p>
<p>But, in a large sense, we can not dedicate - we can not consecrate - we can not hallow - this ground. The brave men, living and dead, who struggled here, have consecrated it, far above our poor power to add or detract. The world will little note, nor long remember what we say here, but it can never forget what they did here. It is for us the living, rather, to be dedicated here to the unfinished work which they who fought here have thus far so nobly advanced. It is rather for us to be here dedicated to the great task remaining before us - that from these honored dead we take increased devotion to that cause for which they gave the last full measure of devotion - that we here highly resolve that these dead shall not have died in vain - that this nation, under God, shall have a new birth of freedom - and that government of the people, by the people, for the people, shall not perish from the earth.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Gettysburg-Address&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Gettysburg-Address&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Gettysburg Address&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gettysburg Address&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four s
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
      <category term="Speech" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/Speech/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Invictus</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/28/Invictus/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/28/Invictus/</id>
    <published>2017-02-28T15:56:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-05T18:47:39.786Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Invictus"><a href="#Invictus" class="headerlink" title="Invictus"></a>Invictus</h2><p>Out of night that covers me,<br>Black as the pit from pole to pole,<br>I thank whatever the god maybe<br>For my unconquerable soul.</p>
<p>In the fell clutch of circumstance<br>I have not winced nor cried aloud.<br>Under the bludgeoning of chance<br>My head is bloody, but unbowed.</p>
<p>Beyond this place of wrath and tears<br>Looms but the Horror of the shade,<br>And yet the menace of the years<br>Finds, and shall find me, unafraid.</p>
<p>It matters not how strait the gate,<br>How charged with punishments the scroll,<br>I am the master of my fate;<br>I am the captain of my soul.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Invictus&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Invictus&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Invictus&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Invictus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of night that covers me,&lt;br&gt;Black as the p
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Poem" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/Poem/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Youth</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/24/Youth/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/24/Youth/</id>
    <published>2017-02-24T13:27:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-03-05T18:41:09.700Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="Youth"><a href="#Youth" class="headerlink" title="Youth"></a>Youth</h2><p>Youth is not time of life; it is a state of mind; it is not a matter the rosy cheeks, red lips and supple knees; it is a matter of the will, a quality of the imagination, a vigor of the emotions; it is the freshness of the deep springs of life.</p>
<p>Youth means a temperamental predominance of courage over timidity, of the appetite for adventure over the love of ease. This often exists in a man of 60 more than a boy of 20. Nobody grows old merely by a number of years. We grow old by deserting our ideals.</p>
<p>Years may wrinkle the skin, but to give up enthusiasm wrinkles the soul. Worry, fear, self-distrust bows the heart and turns the spirit back to dust.</p>
<p>Whether 60 or 16, there is in every human being’s heart the lure of wonder, the unfailing childlike appetite for what’s next and the joy of the game of living. In the center of your heart and my heart there is a wireless station: so long as it receives messages of beauty, hope, cheer, courage and power from men and from the Infinite, so long are you young.</p>
<p>When the aerials are down, and your spirit is covered with snows of cynicism and ice of pessimism, then you are grown old, even at 20; but as long as your aerials are up, to catch waves of optimism, there is hope you may die young at 80.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;Youth&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Youth&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Youth&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Youth&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Youth is not time of life; it is a state of mind; it is no
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>What I Have Lived For</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/24/What-I-Have-Lived-For/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/24/What-I-Have-Lived-For/</id>
    <published>2017-02-24T13:03:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-28T15:54:42.560Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="What-I-Have-Lived-For"><a href="#What-I-Have-Lived-For" class="headerlink" title="What I Have Lived For"></a>What I Have Lived For</h2><p>Three passions, simple but overwhelmingly strong, have governed my life: the longing for love, the search for knowledge, and unbearable pity for the suffering of mankind. These passions, like great winds, have blown me hither and thither, in a wayward course, over a deep ocean of anguish, reaching to the very verge of despair.</p>
<p>I have sought love, first, because it brings ecstasy - ecstasy so great that I would often have sacrificed all the rest of my life for a few hours of this joy. I have sought it, next, because it relieves loneliness - that terrible loneliness in which one shivering consciousness looks over the rim of the world into the cold unfathomable lifeless abyss. I have sought it, finally, because in the union of love I have seen, in a mystic miniature, the prefiguring vision of the heaven that saints and poets have imagined. This is what I sought, and though it might seem too good for human life, this is what - at last - I have found.</p>
<p>With equal passion I have sought knowledge. I have wished to understand the hearts of men. I have wished to know why the stars shine. And I have tried to apprehend the Pythagorean power by which number holds sway above the flux. A little of this, but not much, I have achieved.</p>
<p>Love and Knowledge, so far as they were possible, led upward toward the heavens. But always pity brought me back to earth. Echoes of cries of pain reverberate in my heart. Children in famine, victims tortured by oppressors, helpless old people a hated burden to their sons, and the whole world of loneliness, poverty, and pain make a mockery of what human life should be. I long to alleviate the evil, but I cannot, and I too suffer.</p>
<p>This has been my life. I have found it worth living, and would gladly live it again if the chance were offered me.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;h2 id=&quot;What-I-Have-Lived-For&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#What-I-Have-Lived-For&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;What I Have Lived For&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What I Have Lived For&lt;/
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="BornToWin" scheme="http://blog.sky-line.net/tags/BornToWin/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>与其感慨路难行, 不如马上出发</title>
    <link href="http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/02/better-run-than-curse-the-road/"/>
    <id>http://blog.sky-line.net/2017/02/02/better-run-than-curse-the-road/</id>
    <published>2017-02-02T07:27:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-02T07:44:59.068Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>今天早上去跑了一次步. 因为很久没有跑步所以心肺耐力有点跟不上了, 跑了大概五公里的时候开始犯恶心, 于是慢慢走回来了.</p>
<p>可是人总是要不断的前进, 这才是人生的意义.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;今天早上去跑了一次步. 因为很久没有跑步所以心肺耐力有点跟不上了, 跑了大概五公里的时候开始犯恶心, 于是慢慢走回来了.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是人总是要不断的前进, 这才是人生的意义.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
